Adhithyan Srinivasan

Email - <u>adhicool91@gmail.com</u> Ph no - +91 9994039461

Website - https://adhispace.github.io
https://github.com/adhispace

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/adhithyan-s-275323b4/

Summary

Passionate front end developer with 7.5+ years of experience inclined towards writing clean, minimal and readable code adhering to best practices.

Technologies & Tools -

HTML5, SCSS, Javascript, Typescript, Angular v9, AG-Grid, Chart js, GIT, Jira, Firebase

Experience

1) L&T Infotech

Nov 2020 - present Client - Citi Bank Roles

- Create dashboards using Chart js.
- Fix bugs and do improvement to application.
- Write Unit test cases and perform code review.

2) Renault Nissan Technology Business Centre

Jan 2018 - Oct 2020 Client - Renault Roles

- Create reusable components in Angular
- Co created a tool "Build Your Own Dashboard" which allows users to build their own dashboard for hackathon.
- Write Unit test cases and perform code review.

3) Cognizant Technology Solutions Limited

Sep 2016 - Dec 2017

Client - Verizon Data Services

Roles

- Create admin and devtools for developers.
- Write Unit test cases and maintain test coverage.

4) IBM India Private Limited

Jan 2014 - Sep 2016 Client - IBM Italy Roles

- Create tools for technicians using HTML5, CSS, Javascript
- Create responsive pages with "mobile first" approach.

Education

1) B.Tech - Electronics and Communication Engineering

2008 - 2012

Kalasalingam University

Certification

1) Microsoft Certification - Programming in HTML5 with Javascript and CSS3

Certification ID - 990801719

Personal Projects

1) E Claps - Online contests for kids https://eclaps.in

2) Bookkart - Simple Book searcher app built on top of google books API https://book-kart.vercel.app/

Articles

 Customize angular material component - Datepicker https://medium.com/@adhithyan_s/customize-angular-material-component-d atepicker-88af0666a70d